他们不惧怕十字架
Cross won't repel them.
阳光奈何他们不得
Sunlight won't kill them.
但嗜血是真的
Bloodlust, that part's true.
他喂给你的是吸血鬼的血
That was vampire blood he dosed you with.
觉得光线很强  照的你皮肤难受吗
Lights are too bright? Sunshine hurt your skin?
我好饥渴
I get so hungry.
告诉你一声  报警电话一按就接通
Just so you know, 911's on speed-dial.
克利希  你可以相信我
Krissy, you can trust me.
你爸爸出门了吗
So your dad's on the road right now?
有一阵了
Been gone a while?
我爸爸走了  就没再回来
My dad left, and he didn't come back.
所以我也要一起去
So I'm coming with you.
-门都没有  -我去定了
- No. Hell, no. - I'm coming!
那个服务员为什么要上卡车
Why is that waitress getting into that truck?
不赖嘛  顶个拳嘛  干得漂亮啊
All right. Come on. Give it up. Good work.
你真是个二货
You're a dweeb.
撑住  我来了  迪恩
Hold on -- I got you! Dean!
他帮不了你  没人能帮你
He can't help you. No one can.
那我只能自己来了
I guess I'll have to help myself, then.
我要退休了
I'm retiring.
-这真傻啊  -是啊
- We're so lame. - Yeah, we are.
自己保重
Take care of yourself.
如今
堪萨斯  康威泉
怎么回事
What was that?
怎么了
What?
这儿只有我们  克利希
There's no one out here but us, Krissy.
怎么回事
What?
不  别丢下我啊  艾丹
No. No. Don't leave me here! Aidan!
别丢下我
Don't leave me here!
天呐
Oh, God.
你没事吧
You okay?
真悬啊
That was close.
下次你来做诱饵吧
Next time one of you can be the bait.
是他
It's him.
杀了一个  还有两个
One down. Two to go.
凶鬼恶灵
第八季 第十八集
怪胎和极客
这里是什么情况
So, what are we looking at again?
高速公路边发现两具年轻女子尸体
"Two young women found near the freeway
且遭人割喉
with their throats ripped out."
我看像是吸血鬼
Sounds vampy to me.
或许吧
Yeah, maybe.
如果这个案子你不想参与了
Listen, if you want to take a knee on this one
如果你觉得有点力不从...
if you're not feeling up to it...
什么
What?
就是测试的事  还有小卡的话
You know, the trials, what Cass said,
你的伤他也不能治愈
that you got what he can't cure.
那是什么意思呢
Hmm, which means what, exactly?
我不知道啊  你说呢  你还好吗
Well, I don't know. You tell me. Are you okay?
我很好  你还好吗
I'm fine. Are you okay?
我
Me?
是啊  小卡把你伤得不轻啊
Yeah. Um, Cass dinged you up pretty good.
所以呢
And?
我只想确保你还好
And I just wanted to make sure you're okay.
你是指感情上吗
What, like my feelings?
如果你想谈谈这个  好啊
If that's what you want to talk about, sure.
好吧
Okay.
这么说吧
I'll tell you what.
我去买点草药茶
Why don't I go get some, uh, herbal tea.
-懒得理你  -你去找几个瘾君子牛仔
- Okay. - And you can find some cowboy junkies on the dial.
去死吧  迪恩
Eat me, Dean.
我们就把这事好好聊聊
And you know what? We'll just talk it out.
谈话愉快
Good talk.
那是相当愉快  很健康
Nay, great talk! Very healthy!
联调局
FBI?
你们是为"少女杀手"的案子而来吧
You're here about the lady killer murders, aren't you?
"少女杀手"
The lady killer murders?
嗯  我自己想的名字
Yeah, coined it myself.
恭喜  能跟我们谈谈吗
Congratulations. What can you tell us?
两个死者都是21岁以下的女性
Well, both victims were female, under 21,
重点在于
and here's the kicker --
她们的血都被吸干净了
they were drained of all their blood.
是啊  我们也觉得很奇怪
Exactly. We found that strange, also.
但昨晚  情况变得更怪了
But then last night, things got even stranger.
-昨晚  -对
- Last night? - Yeah.
出于安全考虑  我们在富勒角安了摄像头
We set up a security cam on Fuller's point for safety purposes.
当地的年轻人都去那儿亲热
It's where our local young people like to go make out.
昨晚  发生了疯狂的事
Last night, things got crazy.
真是吓人啊
Hell of a thing, ain't it?
你能认出他们吗
Uh, you I.D. any of these people?
还没有
Well, not yet.
我们赶到时犯罪现场已经清理一空
Crime scene was empty when we got there.
死者也不见了
No vic, no nothing.
我觉得是邪教或是毒品什么的
Uh, I'm thinking it's some kind of cult or a drug thing.
所以我一小时前对这三个人发了全州通告
So I put a statewide A.P.B. Out on these three about an hour ago.
你得取消通告
I'm gonna need you to call that off.
这些带子也得交给我们
And we're gonna need this footage.
什么
What?
警长  你以为我们为什么会来
Sheriff, why do you think we're here?
因为这里牵扯到联邦调查
You just crossed streams with a federal investigation.
所以你还是配合一下  取消全境通告
Now, I suggest you cooperate, call off your A.P.B.,
否则你就吃不了兜着走
or you're gonna find yourself in a world of hurt.
好吧
Right.
刚才是唱的哪一出啊
So, what was that all about, g-man?
还记得克利希・钱伯斯吗
You remember Krissy Chambers?
记得  那起尸鬼的案子
Uh, yeah, the Vetalas case, right?
他们在高速公路的货车停车场下手
They were working that truck stop by the freeway.
她和她父亲帮我们了结了他们
She and her dad helped us shut 'em down.
没错  然后她保证会回归平民
Right, and then he promised to go civilian
将来不会做个猎人
so she wouldn't grow up to be a hunter.
猜猜这部虐杀电影的主角是谁
Well, guess who the star of this snuff film is?
不是吧
Come on.
或许他不知道她在干这个
Well, maybe he doesn't know she's doing this.
大半夜的溜出去
What, sneaking out in the middle of the night
跟一帮小屁孩猎杀怪物
to go hunt monsters with the apple dumpling gang?
现在的孩子就这么找刺激吗
Is that what kids are doing for kicks these days?
那或许他知道  而且在帮她
Okay. Then maybe he knows, and he's helping her out.
然后还被人拍了下来吗
What, get caught on "Candid camera"?
赶快趁她惹出更多麻烦之前找到她吧
Let's just go find her before she gets into any more trouble.
你25了
You're 25?
实际上  我想我40了
Actually, I think I'm 40.
我告诉你了  我有男朋友
I told you... I have a boyfriend.
那你手机里怎么完全没有他的痕迹
Then how come I couldn't find him in your cellie?
因为  我们只视频聊天
Because we only skype.
好吧  我猜猜  他住在加拿大
Right. And let me guess -- he also lives in Canada?
他还真是住在那儿
You know, he does, actually.
一个叫"给姐去死"的小镇
A small town called "Kiss my ass."
好吧
Okay.
但是
But...
我们在车里的时候你可得跟我亲昵点
You sure were giving off a different vibe in the car.
你终于回来了  开始吧
Good. You're back. Let's do this.
吸血鬼最后的影像来自取款机摄像头
Vamp was last seen by an ATM camera
正进入这间旅馆
checking into this hotel.
我黑进了旅馆的摄像头找到了他
I tapped into the hotel's security cams and found him.
215房间
Room 215.
好的
Okay.
开始吧
Let's do this.
有信号吗
You transmitting?
没问题
You bet.
一个人吗
He alone?
不知道
I can't tell.
我们搞一项新仪式怎么样
Hey, how about we start a new tradition,
每次干活儿之前
and before each job,
我们彼此赠吻  以祝好运
we give each other good-luck kisses?
改成我揍你的脖子怎么样
How about I punch you in the throat instead?
你知道你那些小伎俩
You know you're not gonna get anywhere
克利希是不会买账的
with Krissy with those cheesy moves.
你能不能别再数落我
How about you stop putting salt in my game
管好你自己吧
and mind your own business?
血吗
Blood?
克利希
Hey, Krissy.
你们在这儿干什么呢
What are you two doing here?
救你的命
Saving your bacon, that's what.
你觉得我需要你救吗
Does it look like my bacon needs saving?
等等  你们怎么找来的  我一直用现金
Wait. How'd you find me? I paid cash everywhere.
20英里内只有两个旅馆
Only two hotels within a 20-mile radius,
我们也付现金  但付的更多
and we paid cash, too -- just more.
该死的招待员
Freaking clerk.
克利希你爸爸呢
Krissy, where's your dad?
死了
Dead.
我们还是再也别见面了
Well, let's do this again, like, never.
走吧  我们能行的
Now go. We got this.
我们是谁
We who?
什么能行
And got what?
吸血鬼
A vampire.
抱歉  什么
Sorry. A what?
我们进去了  屋里安全
We're in. The room's clear.
只有一个受害者
Nobody here but a vic.
我来
I got him!
你
You --
该死
Son of a bitch.
-得叫辆救护车  -这就到
- We need to call an ambulance! - Ambulance is on its way.
她受惊了  我帮她安定下来
She's in shock. I'll stabilize her.
把她留给医务人员
We'll leave her here for the paramedics.
求你  别开枪
Please! Don't shoot me!
别  别开枪
Don't shoot me! Please, don't --
求你  好疼啊
Please... it hurts so bad!
你怎么这么快就把他放倒了
How did you drop him so quickly?
飞镖里面是死人血
Darts filled with dead man's blood.
蓝货车呢
Where's the blue van?
什么蓝货车
What blue van?
他之前冲着那辆蓝货车跑的
The blue van that he was Usain Bolting it to?
算了
Never mind.
等等
Wait, stop!
他轮不到你来杀
This is not your kill.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
三个月前这个吸血鬼潜入一户人家
Three months ago, this blood banger snuck into a house
杀死了三个正在熟睡的人
and killed three people in their sleep.
什么  不  那不是我
What?! No! I didn't do that!
其中一个女人  她从没伤害过任何人
One was a woman -- never hurt anyone!
另外两个  是一个弟弟和一个妹妹
The other two, a brother and a sister.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我从朋友家回来  就发现了他们
I came home from a friend's house, and I found them.
他们是我的家人
They were my family!
怎么会这样
This isn't happening.
我什么都没做  我发誓
I didn't do anything, I swear.
求你  救救我
Please, help me!
没事的
It's okay.
结束了
It's over.
我们得私下谈谈
We need to talk to you privately.
你认识这家伙吗
You know this guy?
是的  以前认识的
Yeah. We have a past.
好吧  你得跟我讲讲是怎么回事
All right. So, you're gonna have to catch me up.
你爸爸他...
What -- did your dad, uh --
他不能放弃那种生活吗
He couldn't quit the life, could he?
不  他放弃了
No, he did.
有一段时间我们过得很好
For a while, it was amazing.
我们每晚在桌前吃晚饭
We had dinner every night at a table.
我们看电视  去散步  甚至去逛商场
We watched tv, went on walks. Even went to the mall.
后来呢
And then?
后来
And then...
过去追了来
the past came a-knockin'.
我有天早上醒来就发现他死了
I woke up one morning and found him dead....
他的喉咙被割开了
...his throat ripped out.
我很遗憾
Well, I'm sorry.
我也是
Me too.
如果不是约瑟芬和艾丹
If it weren't for Josephine and Aidan,
我肯定活不下来
I don't know how I would have made it.
他们也失去了家人吗
So, they both lost their families, as well?
是的  我们在一起追杀吸血鬼
Yeah, the same vamps we're hunting together --
一个血巢
A nest.
我不想给你浇冷水
Well, look, I am sorry to rain on your parade,
但你太年轻了  不该干这个
but you are way too young to be doing this.
杀怪物没有太年轻一说
You're never too young to kill monsters,
尤其是杀那个杀了你家人的怪物
especially the ones that kill your family.
猎魔不总是杀戮和复仇
Hunting isn't all about killing and revenge.
我们上次不是谈过这个了吗
I thought we had this chat last time.
你有没有...
Do you have any, uh --
亲戚什么的
Do you have any family that's still out there?
辛辛那提有个姨妈  怎么了
An aunt in Cincinnati. Why?
你得收拾东西  我们带你去那儿
'cause you're packing a bag, and we're taking you there.
我看维克多是不会同意的
I think Victor's gonna have a problem with that.
维克多
Victor?
他收留了我们  教会我们一切
He took us in, showed us everything we know.
等等  这是什么情况
Wait. So, what are we talking here?
少年猎魔班吗
Some sort of kid's school for hunters?
别傻了  好吗  我们又不是X战警
Don't be such a dweeb, okay? We're not the x-men.
维克多在帮我们复仇
Victor's helping us get revenge.
我不管他是什么人  他不怎么样
Yeah, well, I don't care what he is. He sucks.
因为你和你的小伙伴被人发现了
'cause you and your little crew here got caught.
要不是我
And if it wasn't for me,
你们的脸就会到处上新闻了
your faces would be splattered all over the news.
那又怎样
Well, you know, so what?!
或许人们也该知道
Maybe it's time that people know the truth
晚上都有些什么恶魔在活动了
about what's really going bump in the night.
引发恐慌  造成伤害吗
Oh, and cause panic? Create mayhem?
真是个好计划
Yeah, that's a great plan.
我用不着你来救  迪恩
Look, I don't need you to save me, Dean.
我不是个小孩子了
I'm not a little kid anymore.
怎么回事
What happened?
小屁孩就这样
Teenagers, that's what.
她跟你说维克多了吗
She tell you about Victor?
说了  什么情况啊
Yeah. What do we think?
我们在斯波坎市不是曾遇到一个
Well, didn't we meet up with a hunter named Victor
叫维克多的猎人吗
one time in Spokane?
那都是哪年的事了
That's a long time ago.
那之后就没有他的音讯了
I haven't heard about him since.
好吧  那么这些孩子...
All right, so, these kids are --
身处危险  不知轻重  当然了
Dangerous and off their meds? Yeah, no kidding.
那怎么办  我们去找这个维克多谈谈
So, what? We go and talk with Victor?
好了吗
Ready?
行了
Okay.
这可不像公社啊
Not what I'd call a compound.
怎么了
What's wrong?
跟我想的不太一样
It's just not what I expected.
你怎么想的
And what was that?
更像《蝇王》
A little more "Lord of the flies""
而不是《考斯比一家》
less Huxtables.
抱歉让你失望了
Sorry to disappoint.
维克多・罗杰斯
Victor Rogers.
我们见过  在华盛顿猎杀食人怪
We met -- a rugaru hunt in Washington.
我是萨姆  这是迪恩
I'm Sam. This is Dean.
对了  温家兄弟
Oh, yes. The Winchesters.
没错
Right.
-好点了吗  -好多了
- Better now? - Much.
我们怎么说
And what do we always say?
向前看  但永不遗忘
Move on, but never forget.
很好  你明早不是有三角学测试吗
Good. Now, don't you have a trig test in the morning?
我没事  维克  没有测试
Oh, I'm good, Vic. No test.
我去冷静一下  打打游戏
I'm just gonna chill, play video games. Uh-huh.
做梦吧
Yeah, keep dreaming.
我都两次让你清理房间了
Because I asked you to clean your room twice,
你还是没做
and you still haven't done it.
快去吧
Go on.
还有你
And you.
明早会把行动报告放在你桌上
A full report about the hunt on your desk by morning.
好的  我回屋了
Okay. I'll be in my room.
喝一杯
Drink?
好啊
Sure.
这些孩子还去上学
So, these kids go to school --
正常的那种学校吗
like, school-school, real school?
是的  而且他们表现很好
Yes, and they're doing incredibly well
尤其考虑到他们的遭遇
considering all they've been through.
好吧  你们怎么运作的
Okay, so how does this work?
先练练足球
What, after -- after soccer practice
或者去卖面包
and -- and the bake sale,
然后去砍掉吸血鬼的脑袋吗
they, uh, chop vampires' heads off?
是啊
Well, yeah.
我认为兼顾才是上策  对吧
I think a balanced approach is best, don't you?
但他们还只是孩子
But they're kids.
他们就不该猎魔
They shouldn't be hunting at all.
你必须立即停止这一切
You got to break this up right now.
我找到他们时  他们失落  不解和愤怒
When I found them, they were lost, confused, angry.
我给了他们家庭和目标
I gave them family and purpose.
你想打破这一切  为什么
And you want to take all that away? Why?
这样他们就不会死于非命了
So they don't get killed.
他们知道这行的风险
They know the risks.
可是为什么要冒这个险
Yeah, but why take them?
因为下一代的猎人必须更强更好
Because the next generation of hunters has to be better.
比什么更强更好
Better than what?
我们
Better than us.
得了  伙计们
Oh, come on, guys.
我了解你们的朋友  马丁是个疯子
I know your friends. I mean, Martin was insane.
盖思显然小时候被人头朝下摔过
And somebody obviously dropped Garth on his head when he was a baby.
我知道你们很爱那个鲍比
And I know you two loved that Bobby guy,
但他就是个没用的老酒鬼
but he was a barely functional alcoholic.
说话小心点
Watch it.
我无意冒犯
No disrespect meant,
但约瑟芬是州代表运动员和全国优秀学者
but Josephine is an all-state athlete and national merit scholar.
艾丹能在瞬间把你的钱包顺走
Aidan is so fast he could pick your pocket before you could even blink.
至于克利希
And Krissy,
她就是天生的领袖和猎人
oh, she's just a natural-born leader and hunter.
那又如何
So what?
这些孩子是人中翘楚
So these kids are the cream of the crop.
他们就是披头士  是梦之队
They are the Beatles. They are the dream team.
等他们完成复仇后
And once they get their revenge...
他们会成为我们可望而不可即的优秀猎人
...they'll be better hunters than any of us ever dreamed of.
太疯狂了
This is crazy.
是吗  他们过得挺好啊
Is it? They got a pretty good life.
孩子不应该参与猎魔  萨姆
Kids aren't supposed to hunt, Sam.
我们当年就是
We did.
是啊  看看我们的下场
Yeah, and look what that did for us.
或许他们这么处理很得当
Well, maybe they're doing it right.
也许他们能一边猎魔一边好好生活
Maybe they can hunt and have a real life.
你知道那不可能
You know that's not true.
为什么  因为我们没做到
Why? 'cause it didn't work for us?
因为就没人做到过
Because it doesn't work for anybody.
好吧  那你想怎样
Okay, then what do you want to do?
维克多才不会收手
'cause Victor's not gonna stop this.
-他们说他们在找血巢对吧  -对
- They said they were hunting a nest, right? - Yeah.
那我们去替他们找
Well, let's hunt it for 'em.
这样我们想到办法对付维克多前
Well, that way, until we can figure out what to do with Victor,
能保他们平安
they stay safe.
好吧
All right, um...
你打算怎么着手
So, what's your move?
我想跟那个被绑在旅馆里的姑娘谈谈
I want to talk to that girl who was tied up at the hotel.
我总觉得那事不太对劲
Something didn't smell right about that.
你留下照顾这个脱线家族吧
Why don't you stay here and look after the Brady Bunch?
萨姆  来得正好
Sam, just in time.
-坐  -华夫饼吗
- Grab a seat. - Waffles?
是啊  克利希的最爱
Yeah, Krissy's fav.
我爸爸以前总给我做这个
My dad used to make 'em for me all the time.
我觉得他就只会做这个
I think it was the only thing he knew how to cook.
交谈
Interact.
是啊  书呆子
Yeah, nerd.
注意点礼貌
And you -- manners.
我们要迟到了
We're gonna be late.
快点
Come on.
带好自己的东西
Grab your stuff.
-放学我去接你们  -再见
- I'll pick you up after school. - See ya.
-快如闪电是吧  -是啊
- Whirlwind, right? - Yeah.
孩子们就是这样的
It's always like that with kids.
你有孩子吗
You got any?
我  没有
Me? Uh, no.
不想造一两个
You want any?
不知道
Uh, I don't know.
相信我  要孩子吧
Trust me, the answer's yes.
这是你的孩子
These yours?
是
Yeah.
不过我们去野营时
Well, until we went camping
他们被一只雪怪撕成碎片了
and a Wendigo ripped them to shreds.
抱歉
Sorry.
所以你才收留这些孩子吗
Is that why you're doing this, taking all these kids in?
知道我意识到了什么吗  萨姆
But you know what I realized, Sam,
这些孩子不必走我们的老路
is that these kids,they don't have to live it the way we have.
总住在糟糕的旅馆  不停地奔波
You know, crappy hotel rooms, always moving,
没有家人  也没有自己的生活
no family, no life.
并不非得那样
It's not the only way.
我和警察都说过了
Like I told the cops already,
我不知道吉米・戴为什么会做那种事
I'm not sure why Jimmy Day would do something like this.
吉米・戴
Jimmy Day?
你认识绑架你的人
Wait, so you knew the guy that grabbed you?
镇上的人都认识吉米  他是个英雄
Everyone in town knows Jimmy, he's a hero.
他从阿富汗回来时
We had a parade for him
我们在市区为他举行了游行庆祝
downtown when he came back from Afghanistan.
对不起  那是什么时候
Uh, sorry. When was this?
几周前
A few weeks ago.
这个叫吉米・戴的人
So, uh... this Jimmy Day guy,
他就那么抓了你  把你带去了旅馆
he...he just grabbed you and took you to the hotel?
不是
No.
我下班回家走到停车场时
I-I came from work and was in the parking lot
有辆蓝货车停了下来
when this blue van pulled up.
有个穿连帽衫的人向我问路
This guy with a hoodie asked me directions.
我就记得这么多
That's all I remember,
然后就醒来发现自己被绑在床上
till I woke up tied to that bed.
穿连帽衫的人也在吗
And was hoodie there, too?
只有吉米在
Just Jimmy,
他在哭  还说对不起之类的话
and he was crying, saying he was sorry and all.
他说对不起
That he was sorry?
一开始我以为他要杀了我
At first I thought he was gonna kill me.
但后来  他显得很害怕
But then he just... he just seemed scared.
怎么回来了
Hey. What happened to school?
维克多把我们叫回来了
Victor pulled us out.
为什么
Why?
因为我们又找到了一个目标
Cause we've found another target.
谁
Who?
杀害克利希父亲的那个吸血鬼
The vamp that killed Krissy's dad.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
好的
Okay.
在附近加油站的摄像头里发现了这个
Pulled this from a security camera at a nearby gas station.
等一下  我们怎么确定就是她
Wait, how do we know this is definitely her?
警方的素描  受害者的叙述
Police sketch, victim's accounts...
还有这个
...and this.
我父亲的项链
My dad's necklace.
我妈妈在结婚纪念日给他的
My mom gave it to him on their anniversary.
你确定这是摄像头拍到的
Are you sure this is a video surveillance pic?
就是她
It's her!
失陪一下
Excuse me.
你在吗
Hey. You there?
跟那女孩谈得如何
Yeah. How did it go with the girl?
很奇怪  也许那个吸血鬼没有说谎
Strange. Might be that vampire wasn't lying.
他是近一个月刚转化的
He was fresh made within the month,
但约瑟芬的家人是三个月前被杀害的
But Josephine's family was murdered three months ago.
那谁杀了他们
So, who killed them, then?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我想找那个开蓝货车的人谈谈
I'd like to talk to whoever's driving that blue van.
除此之外  你那边呢
Other than that...you?
出事了
Something's up.
维克多声称他拿到了一张
Victor says he has a surveillance photo
杀害克利希家人的吸血鬼的监控图像
of the vampire that killed Krissy's father.
但是迪恩  我觉得不是
But, Dean... I'm not so sure.
为什么
Why's that?
那上面没有时间水印
There's no time stamp on it.
好吧  你觉得他在说谎
Okay. So you think he's lying?
或许他只是弄错了  很难说
Well, that, or he's just wrong. It's hard to say.
我从不信任穿毛衣的人
Yeah, I never trust a guy who wears a sweater.
你要我回去吗
You want me to head back there?
不用  我一人可以  我再做一些调查
No, no. I'm good. Let me do some more digging.
好的  我去找旅馆招待员谈谈
All right. I'm gonna talk to the hotel clerk,
看看他知道些什么
see what he knows.
大家都去哪了
Hey. Where did everybody go?
追踪那个吸血鬼了
Tracking that vamp.
我们有一个离家更近的麻烦
Well, I think we got a problem a lot closer to home.
看看这个
Look at this.
看到那蓝货车了吗
See that blue van?
我哥哥昨天在旅馆外面看到过
My brother saw it outside the hotel yesterday.
我们认为他和那吸血鬼是一伙的
We think he's working with the vampire we popped.
看来我们有事干了
Looks like we're going huntin'.
很高兴再次见到你
Ahh. Nice to see you again.
是啊  我就知道
Yeah, I bet. Listen,
我想知道昨天是谁住进了215房间
I need to know who, uh, checked into room 215 yesterday.
是一个穿连帽衫的人
It was some guy wearing a hoodie,
很难辨认出他的脸
so it was hard to make out his face.
他是不是开一辆蓝货车
He drive a blue van, by any chance?
我看起来像停车员吗
Do I look like a valet?
他拿了一个宣传册
He took one of those.
哪一个
Which one?
上面有"旅馆"的那个
The one that says "Lodg"" On it.
"康威泉旅馆"
"Conway springs lodge."
是的  夏季时很火爆
Yep, big during the summer season.
但每年这个时候歇业
But this time of year, it's closed.
从这儿到那里有多远
How far away is it from here?
大概有几英里
Oh, it's a couple miles down the road.
你是谁
Who the hell are you?!
回答我
Answer me!
停下吧
Please make it go away.
我好痛
It hurts so much.
什么
What? Wha...
别  把灯关上  太亮了
No, shut them off! They're too bright!
你先告诉我是怎么回事
Not till you tell me what the hell's going on here.
我不知道
I don't know!
我这是怎么了
What's happening to me?
过来
Come here.
你以前从没发生过这种情况吗
That's never happened to you before?
没有  没有  我有些不对劲
No. No, there's something wrong with me.
那个人  他对我做了什么
That -- that guy, he did something to me.
-哪个人  -我不认识
- What guy? - I don't know!
一个开蓝货车的人  他掳走我
This guy in a blue van, he -- he grabbed me.
把我带到这里
He took me here.
我的胃
Oh, my stomach.
真的好痛
It hurts so much.
迪恩
Dean!
把枪放下  我们谈谈
Put those away, and we can talk.
你为什么和杀死我爸的吸血鬼在一起
Why are you with the vampire that killed my dad?
你找错人了
You're barking up the wrong tree.
她不是杀你爸的凶手
She didn't kill your pops.
我不想伤害你  迪恩
I don't want to hurt you, Dean,
但你不走开我不会手软的
but I will if you don't move.
听我说  克利希
Listen to me, Krissy.
她是无辜的
She's innocent.
你怎么知道
And how would you know that?
因为她是新转化的  只有一两天
Because she's fresh made, a day or two.
她爸爸死于几个月前
Her dad was killed months ago.
这件事有蹊跷
This whole thing stinks.
昨晚我们杀死的那个吸血鬼
That vamp that we killed last night?
他为什么发誓他没做什么
Why was he swearing that he didn't do it?
因为他在撒谎
Because he was a liar.
吸血鬼不会求饶  他们只进攻
Vampires don't beg for their lives. They attack.
这是我最后一次客气地说了
Look, last time I'm gonna ask you nicely.
把枪放下  否则有人会受伤
Take the damn guns off me, or somebody's gonna get hurt.
吹牛吧
Big talk.
可不是嘛
I know. It is, isn't it?
就算她不是杀死我爸爸的吸血鬼
So, let's say this isn't the vamp who killed my dad.
她仍然是个恶魔  理应受死
She's still a monster and deserves to die.
如果能救她就不必了
Not if we can save her.
什么
What?
她还没有吸血
She hasn't fed yet.
我们能逆转化  只需给她喝下转化者的血
We can reverse this if we find her maker and get his blood.
我们为什么要在乎她
And why should we care about her?
我说过  猎魔不总是杀戮
Like I said, hunting isn't always about killing.
算了吧
Oh, please.
去跟别人说吧  我们才不信
Preach to some other choir. We're not buying it.
你们想杀死无辜的女孩吗
You want to kill an innocent girl?!
我想让杀死我爸爸的吸血鬼以命抵命
I want the blood sucker who killed my dad to pay.
我们会查出凶手
And we're gonna find out who that is.
但别残忍到随便杀个人解恨
But let's not be so bloodthirsty that just anyone will do.
但维克多说凶手就是她
But Victor says it's her.
但我说不是
And I say it ain't!
我们把她带上
So we're gonna pack her to go,
去找维克多当面对质
and we're gonna ask Victor ourselves.
行吗
Okay?
你醒了  太好了
You're awake. Good.
我们时间不多了
We don't have much time.
干什么
For what?
想象一下
Picture this.
孩子们凯旋归来
The kids arrive home victorious,
却发现你死在客厅里
only to find you dead in their living room.
貌似他们猎杀的血巢
It seems that nest of vampires they were hunting
来复仇了
were seeking revenge...
还杀了你
...and killed you.
这样就激励他们继续猎杀
Thus, inspiring them to hunt even more.
抱歉了  萨姆
I'm sorry, Sam.
我不能让任何人毒害我孩子的思想
I can't have anyone poisoning my kids' minds.
你是说  除了你自己
Other than yourself, that is.
我不必向你和你那个
I don't need to justify my actions to you
自以为是的哥哥解释我的所作所为
or your self-righteous ass of a brother!
你是指你和吸血鬼合作的事吗
You mean like why you're working with a vampire?
这对他有什么好处  可以肆意游荡吗
So what's he get out of this? Free roaming rights?
我们在打仗  一场要输了的仗
We are at war -- a war that we are losing.
利维坦一事的惨败就是一记警钟
That leviathan fiasco was a wake-up call.
为了活下去  我们得无所不用其极
We have to do what we can to survive.
我不指望你会理解
But I wouldn't expect you to understand.
你不是一个父亲
You're not a father.
你不知道
You don't know what it's like
听到孩子濒死的哭喊是什么滋味
to hear the cries of your children dying.
现在我有机会改过
But now I have a second chance to make it all right,
有机会创造下一代猎人
to create the next generation of hunters --
让他们更强  更快  更聪明
Stronger, faster, smarter.
我们回来了
Hey, we're home.
发生什么事了
What is going on here?
这两个人不可信
These two are not to be trusted.
他们要毁掉我们
They're trying to destroy us.
你认识这个吸血鬼吗  维克多
Do you know this vamp, Victor?
他当然认识  他们俩是一伙的
Of course he does! They're working together!
这是真的吗
Is that true?
一言难尽
It's complicated.
不  一点不难
No, actually, it's not.
这个开蓝货车的一直在制造新吸血鬼
See, blue van here's been turning fresh vamps
然后制造机会让你们轻松杀死他们
and setting them up for you kids as easy kills.
为什么
But why?
因为他们根本没杀我们的家人  对吧
Because they didn't kill our families, did they?
是的
No.
那是谁干的
Well, then who did?
我干的
I did.
他们都哭喊过...
And they all screamed...
求我饶命  尤其是那些孩子
...and begged for mercy, especially the little ones.
够了  塞斯
Enough, Seth!
你们必须理解
You have to understand.
我有办法让未来更美好
I saw a way to make the future better.
为了那个美好未来  我必须下狠手
But to get there, I had to do something hard.
你指使他杀了我们的亲人吗
He killed them off your orders?
你们需要动力
You needed motivation.
我考察过你们每一个人
I scouted each and every one of you.
我知道只有这样  你们才会走这条路
And knew it was the only way to get you to hunt.
那你就杀了我们的家人
So you killed our families?
我知道他们的死很惨
I know the deaths are tragic.
但想想你们强强联手
But think of all the future lives
将来能拯救多少生命吧
that will now be saved because you are now together.
那些假吸血鬼只是你的训练手段
So, these fake vampires were just a way for you to train us
给我们灌输谎言吗
and fill our heads with lies?!
你们还不明白吗
Don't you see?
这比我们所有人都重要
This is bigger than all of us.
我们要以大局为重
We have to learn to put things in perspective.
跟我走吧
Come with me.
我们可以不计前嫌
We can get past this.
这太不幸了
That is unfortunate.
艾丹
Aidan!
我们要走了
We're leaving.
这不可能
That's not happening.
你会的一切都是我教的
I taught you everything you know.
别逼我伤害你
Don't make me hurt you.
不都是你教的  维克多
Not everything, Victor.
克利希  别
Krissy, don't.
如果我们想为家人复仇
If we want revenge for our families' deaths,
就得拿他下手
he gives it to us!
我们不杀人
We don't kill people.
你也不能杀人
You don't kill people.
他不是人  他是个怪物
He's not a person. He's a monster.
克利希  不管我们怎么做  都不会有好结果
Krissy, this ends bad, no matter what we do.
的确
Exactly.
克利希  别
Krissy, don't.
这枪是为我爸爸还你的
This is for my dad.
这是为约瑟芬一家
For Josephine's family.
这是为艾丹
For Aidan.
这是为我自己
For me.
我们就让他活着
So, we're just gonna let him live?
是的
Yeah.
让他孤独一人活着
All alone, with himself.
没有家人  没有朋友
No family. No friends.
依我看这就够了
Ask me, that's not much of anything.
我们去救那个女孩
Let's save that girl.
枪
Gun!
慢点喝
Just drink slowly.
这能帮你消除疼痛
This will take away all the pain.
真为你骄傲
Proud of you.
趁我没打你赶紧闭嘴
Shut up, before I punch you.
她怎么样了
So, how's she doing?
现在好多了
Better now.
我想这个是你的
I think this is yours.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我去外面等
I'll wait outside.
好吧
Okay.
我们在车里  你准备好了就出来
Whenever you're ready, we'll be in the car.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你姨妈  辛辛那提  普通的生活
Your aunt? Cincinnati? Normal life?
我们明天午饭时就能到
We'll be there by lunch tomorrow.
虽然我们因为阴谋和惨剧相识  但是
Look, I hate how we were put together, but...
我不能否认这感觉很好
I can't deny that it feels right.
为什么要让维克多把这也毁了呢
And why should I let Victor ruin that, too?
你的意思是
So, what you're saying is that
你喜欢那边那个男孩  你想留下
you like that boy over there and you want to stay?
什么  艾丹  才不是
What? Aidan? No.
我是说他就像我哥哥
I mean... he's like my brother.
根本不是你说的那样
It's nothing like that.
你们还是未成年人
Well, you're all still minors.
没多久了
Not for long.
约瑟芬还有几个月就满18岁了
Josephine will be 18 in a few months.
我们在这里有一份生活  也有彼此
And we all have a life and each other here.
猎魔呢
And hunting?
我们不会主动去的
We won't go looking for it.
但如果附近出现了怪物
But if any monsters show up around here,
他们最好小心点
they better look out.
好吧  很好
Okay. Good.
真的吗
Really?
我以为我还需要跟你费一番口舌呢
I thought I was gonna have to fight you way more on that.
你说得对  你不是小孩子了
Well, you're right. You're not a kid anymore.
你可以自己做主
You can make your own decisions.
作为一个老古董你还不赖
You're all right for an old guy.
我真没那么老呢
I'm really not that old.
对着镜子说去吧
You keep telling yourself that.
行了  我会找...
All right. Well, I'm gonna have a, uh --
找人每隔一阵子就过来看看你们
a guy come and check on you every once in a while, okay?
他叫盖思
His name is Garth.
他会来确认你们平安  缺不缺什么
He'll make sure that you're all right and you got what you need.
-盖思  -对
- Garth? - Yeah.
一开始会觉得他怪  但慢慢会喜欢他的
He's a little strange at first, but you'll come to love him.
保重  迪恩
Take care, Dean.
对  再见  迪恩
Yeah. Goodbye, Dean.
艾丹
Aidan.
听着  有些...
Listen, there's, uh,
有些关于克利希的事我想告诉你
something I want to tell you about Krissy.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
如果我伤害她你会杀了我
You'll kill me if I ever hurt her.
什么什么的
Blah. Blah. Blah.
不不  她会杀了你
No, no. No. She'll kill you.
祝你好运
Good luck.
这样很好
This is good.
是吗
Is it?
本可能更糟的
Could have been a lot worse.
如果我们不尽快关上地狱之门就会更糟了
Will be if we don't shut those gates of hell soon.
他们跟这事有什么关系
What do they have to do with any of that?
他们现在是猎人了
They're hunters now.
猎人是没有回头路的
You don't just walk away from that.
只有一条出路
There's only one way out of that,
你我都知道这路不怎么好
and you and I both know it ain't pretty.
也许他们会不一样呢
Maybe they'll be different.
也许我们能永远关闭地狱之门
Or maybe if we shut that hell hole once and for and all,
他们三个就能有自己的生活了
Those three can have a real life.
也许不止他们可以有
Maybe they won't be the only ones.